Hello‚ It is me
I was wondering if after all these years You had like to met
To go over everything
They say that time′s supposed to heal ya
But I ain′t done much healing
Hello‚ can you hear me?
I am in California dreaming about who we used to be
When we were younger and free
I have forgotten how it felt before the world fell at our feet
There′s such a difference between us
And a million miles
Hello from the other side
I must have called a thousand times
To tell you I am sorry for everything that I have done
But when I call you never seem to be home
Hello from the outside
At least I can say that I have tried
To tell you I am sorry for breaking your heart
But it don′t matter. It clearly doesn′t tear you apart anymore
Hello‚ how are you?
It is so typical of me to talk about myself. I am sorry
I hope that You are well
Did you ever make it out of that town where nothing ever happened?
And It is no secret that the both of us
Are running out of time
So hello from the other side (other side)
I must have called a thousand times (thousand times)
To tell you I am sorry for everything that I have done
But when I call you never seem to be home
Hello from the outside (outside)
At least I can say that I have tried (I have tried)
To tell you I am sorry for breaking your heart
But it don′t matter. It clearly doesn′t tear you apart anymore
(Highs‚ highs‚ highs‚ highs
Lows‚ lows‚ lows‚ lows)
Anymore
(Highs‚ highs‚ highs‚ highs
Lows‚ lows‚ lows‚ lows)
Anymore
(Highs‚ highs‚ highs‚ highs
Lows‚ lows‚ lows‚ lows)
Anymore
(Highs‚ highs‚ highs‚ highs
Lows‚ lows‚ lows‚ lows)
Anymore
Hello from the other side (other side)
I must have called a thousand times (thousand times)
To tell you I am sorry for everything that I have done
But when I call you never seem to be home
Hello from the outside (outside)
At least I can say that I have tried (I have tried)
To tell you I am sorry for breaking your heart
But it don′t matter. It clearly doesn′t tear you apart anymore
www.RentAnAdviser.com